export const quiz = {
    topic: 'Javascript',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 4,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What does HTML stand for ?',
        choices: ['HyperText Markup Language', 'Hyper texture Markup Language', 'HomeText Markup Language', 'HyperText Making Language'],
        type: 'MCQ', 
        correctAnswer: 'HyperText Markup Language',
      },
      {
        question: 'Are the HTML tags and elements the same thing?',
        choices: ['No. HTML elements are defined by a starting tag, may contain some content and a closing tag.', 'No. HTML elements are defined by a starting tag and a closing tag.', 'Yes. the same thing ', 'yes.HTML elements and tags are defined by a starting tag and a closing ta'],
        type: 'MCQ', 
        correctAnswer: 'No. HTML elements are defined by a starting tag, may contain some content and a closing tag.',
      },
      {
        question: 'What are tags and attributes in HTML?',
        choices: ['Tags are component of the HTML that defines how the content will be structured and  whereas Attributes are used along with the HTML tags to define the characteristics of the element', 'Tags are attributes of the HTML that defines how the content will be structured', 'tags and attributes is components in JS', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ', 
        correctAnswer: 'Tags are component of the HTML that defines how the content will be structured and  whereas Attributes are used along with the HTML tags to define the characteristics of the element',
      },
      {
        question: 'What are void elements in HTML?',
        choices: ['None of these answers', 'HTML attributes which do not have closing tags', 'HTML elements which do not display on the browser', 'HTML elements which do not have closing tags'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'HTML elements which do not have closing tags',
      },
      {
        question: '5. What are HTML Entities ?',
        choices: ['characters are reserved like 1.6,1.7,2.9', 'characters are reserved like <, >, /, etc.', 'characters are reserved like ABCD...', 'All of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'characters are reserved like <, >, /, etc.',
      },      
      {
        question: 'What are different types of lists in HTML?',
        choices: ['Horizontal and vertical', 'Bullets and numbers', 'Ordered and unordered', 'Data stractures'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Ordered and unordered',
      },      
      {
        question: 'What is the class attribute in HTML',
        choices: ['Specify the class name for an HTML element.', 'Attribute that allows design in the CSS file', 'A and B', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Specify the class name for an HTML element.',
      },      
      {
        question: 'What is the difference between the id attribute and the class attribute of HTML elements?',
        choices: ['Multiple elements in HTML can have the same class value, whereas a value of id attribute of one element cannot be associated with another HTML element.', 'Multiple elements in HTML can have the same id value, whereas a value of class attribute of one element cannot be associated with another HTML element.', 'Same thing', 'HTML elements can have class or id'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Multiple elements in HTML can have the same class value, whereas a value of id attribute of one element cannot be associated with another HTML element.',
      },
      {
        question: 'How to optimize website assets loading?',
        choices: ['CDN hosting', 'Lazy Loading', 'Parallel downloads', 'Minify scripts','All the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'All the above',
      },  
      {
        question: 'What is not formatting tags in HTML?',
        choices: ['<b>', '<i>', '<big>', '<inl>'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: '<inl>',
      },  
      {
        question: 'What is the significance of <head> and <body> tag in HTML ?',
        choices: ['The <head> tag is used to contain metadata and external resources of a webpage, while the <body> tag contains the visible content that is displayed in the browser.', 'head is necessary for writing html code and body dont', 'The <body> tag is used to contain metadata and external resources of a webpage, while the <head> tag contains the visible content that is displayed in the browser.'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'The <head> tag is used to contain metadata and external resources of a webpage, while the <body> tag contains the visible content that is displayed in the browser.',
      },  
      {
        question: 'Can we display a web page inside a web page or Is nesting of webpages possible?',
        choices: ['Yes', 'No'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Yes',
      },  
      {
        question: 'Is it possible to change an inline element into a block level element ?',
        choices: ['Yes', 'No', 'Only on HTML5'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Yes',
      },  
      {
        question: 'what from the answers is a way to display HTML elements?',
        choices: ['Inline', 'Block', 'Grid', 'All of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
      },  
      {
        question: 'what from the answers is not value of target attribute?',
        choices: ['_self', '_blank', '_parent', '_next'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: '_next',
      },  
      {
        question: 'In how many ways can we specify the CSS styles for the HTML element?',
        choices: ['Inline External and Internal', 'File tag and parenthesis', 'Inline', 'All of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Inline External and Internal',
      },  
      {
        question: 'How to include javascript code in HTML ?',
        choices: ['Import to the file', 'With <script> tag', 'You can not add script to HTML file', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'With <script> tag',
      },  
      {
        question: 'What are forms in HTML?',
        choices: ['collect the user inputs.', 'element the respresents container', 'Text font', 'Data stractures'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'collect the user inputs.',
      },  
      {
        question: 'What art the difference between SVG and Canvas HTML5 element ?',
        choices: ['The SVG element in HTML5 is resolution-independent and defines graphics using XML, while the Canvas element is a bitmap-based element where graphics are drawn using JavaScript.', 'The Canvas element in HTML5 is resolution-independent and defines graphics using XML, while the SVG element is a bitmap-based element where graphics are drawn using JavaScript.', 'They are the same'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'The SVG element in HTML5 is resolution-independent and defines graphics using XML, while the Canvas element is a bitmap-based element where graphics are drawn using JavaScript.',
      },  
      {
        question: 'What are the types of web storage in HTML5?',
        choices: ['Browser Storage and Cockies', 'External Storage and Internal Storage', 'Local Storage  and Session Storage','All of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Local Storage  and Session Storage',
      },  
    ],
  };
  